tracking202.com 2019-07-16

# Your Privacy Rights - Prosper202 Self-Hosted Tracking ClickServer & Analytics Platform For Digital Marketers

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Prosper202.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Prosper202.com's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Prosper202.com's visitors use its website. From time to time, Prosper202.com may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

Prosper202.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Prosper202.com does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Prosper202.com's websites choose to interact with Prosper202.com in ways that require Prosper202.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Prosper202.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who use our forums to provide a username and email address. In each case, Prosper202.com collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Prosper202.com. Prosper202.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**

Prosper202.com may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Prosper202.com may reveal how many downloads a particular version got, or say which plugins are most popular based on checks from api.Prosper202.com, a web service used by Prosper202 installations to check for new versions of Prosper202 and plugins. However, Prosper202.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Personally-Identifying Information**

We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our web site. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use both personally identifiable information (e.g., your name, phone number, physical or electronic address) and non- personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) or Networking Advertising Initiative at [www.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices).

As well as:  
“California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Company who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of their personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. You may request a list of all of the third parties with whom we share your PII by sending an e-mail to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and place “California Third Party Disclosure” in the subject line. Please allow up to thirty days for a response.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Prosper202.com uses cookies to help Prosper202.com identify and track visitors, their usage of Prosper202.com website, and their website access preferences. Prosper202.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Prosper202.com's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Prosper202.com's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Prosper202.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Prosper202.com's sole discretion. Prosper202.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
